[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Just follow the on-screen instructions as you ____ the discussion forum from within a course.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Abnormal results do not diagnose birth defects, they just ____ that follow-up tests are necessary for further clarification.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Marat used his ____ ideas to arouse the people, and set himself apart.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What did Louis XIV hope to ____ in his domestic and foreign policies?", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is so passive in German class. It's no wonder that she can ____ speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "China did not multiply nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its ____ potential.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not pleasant to contemplate the results of a German ____ in World War II.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you ____ will come from the M31 incident - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because southern Christian churches benefited financially from slave-based plantations they did nothing to ____ the practice of slavery.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you don't need your old furniture, you could ____ it to the youth club.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to exploit the ____ mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Badly- behaved students often ____ the learning of other students in the class.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A new class of antibiotic drugs is not expected to appear in the ____ future.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Which do you ____ the more: health or wealth?", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A regular driving license does not ____ the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He has a ____ knowledge of computer technology.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The final examination shall be designed to ____ a period not to exceed two hours.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people think that electronic toys and games ____ children's creativity.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists have not been able to ____ that the fossil is in fact that of a dinosaur.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are consistent with the popular belief that alcohol intoxication causes males to ____ women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Being the best tennis player in grade 7 is not enough to ____ you for the ISST sports competition.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that ____ to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "German businesses have started to employ an increasing number of older people. They are often better, more ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school has made the difficult ____ to ban the wearing of religious symbols in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our ____ is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) tend to propose unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Poor results in end of year tests often ____ that the teacher has not taught the course very well.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Good teaching is a ____ of fairness, firmness and friendliness.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students gain professional experience before graduation so that they enter the job market with a ____ advantage.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's good that the school ____s ____ new, young teachers every year. They can stimulate discussions about teaching methods.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A common task in the English classroom is to ____ the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company does a minor amount of business in the USA; the ____ of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All political parties have websites these days to ____ people of their policies.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not ____ enough to identify exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I like teachers who can ____ clearly what we have to do.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a ____ transition.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nancy Tsai knew from ____ that the housing situation for graduate students living off campus was bleak.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the demonstrations continue much longer, they will ____ the government to change its plans.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will need to request a ____ leave of absence with USC if you intend to be away from more than 3 days.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will find reference books on this shelf and the ____ ones.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ your efforts you have a good chance of exiting ESL at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "San Francisco's ____ reform program is barely alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a logical ____ of having free will.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ ignorance was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to transform it into a ____ project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is going to ____ a law that will prohibit smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova ____ an identical approach and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people today agree with the ____ that men and women are equal.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police have arrested a man who they say is a ____ of a terrorist organization.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the state was not able to ____ discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm ____ was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should do more to ____ immigrants who do not speak English.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The media and the public should not blame the music ____ for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to appeal to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to ____ Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to ____ in sufficient detail the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her frequent absence from school is the ____ reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will need to get your parents' ____ for your attendance at the sex education classes.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "That plan specifies that only the top 12.5 percent of California high school graduates should be considered ____ for UC admission.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Even though the right hemisphere could not ____ to observers what stimuli it had been presented with, it did show some verbal comprehension.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care reform ____ failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is set to reject the parents' ____ to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her writing was poor in every respect; it was difficult to ____ her biggest problem.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was no ____ to the spread of the disease.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to seek additional funds if the amount of the ____ is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This may ____ relationships between children and parents, and necessitate the involvement of child welfare services.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "At some time in the future we will need to make a total ____ from fossil fuel power, such as coal and oil, to renewable fuels such wind or sun energy.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an ____ against bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ your feet from the table! People have to eat here!", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors usually ____ patients to have some proof of ability to pay for treatment.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the sports of mountain-climbing and table tennis. In the first you can get killed; in the second usually not.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to ____ the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are worth it!", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or ____ admission.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a ____ speed at all heights.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ in turning on the computer. The monitor isn't working.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between learning your first language and learning a second one.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although his letter did not ____ Atlanta as the location of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Elders says that the U.S. must ____ its sick health care system.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't ____ a lecture from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have ____ that students are more likely to complete a community health project if they join a team.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If a student is not in attendance during the last ____ of a semester, the instructor may report a grade of zero.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The picture on the left is the ____ picture. That on the right is a copy.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the ____ word to convey an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school has decided to ____ a ban on smoking anywhere on campus. This also applies to teachers.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final opportunity to ____ with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has set a clear ____ on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the atmosphere every year.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear power stations is ____ the most serious issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nowadays nobody attempts to ____ that smoking is bad for the health.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want an ____ answer to almost any question you could ask, then Google will probably give it to you.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer ____ or modify grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to ____ and collaborate with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to retain employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with ____ to top performers.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new team coach is an ____ of the view: No pain, no gain!", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Not everyone likes ____ webpages with lots of movement and sound.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Board of Trustees met in April 2006 to discuss this report, and decided to ____ the construction of a 500 kW turbine.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his intention to ____ the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without ____ to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Asia is our closest ____ and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and exchange culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A verbal contract is impossible to prove, and the organization will always ____ that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Do you have a ____ pencil? I forgot to bring mine.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For the last 30 years scientists have been searching for a good ____ to gasoline (petrol) as a fuel to run cars.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You have written a very clear and ____ report. Well done!", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is to the government's ____ that they refused to participate in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and occasionally requires travel away from the normal ____ station.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ocean is a ____ of both freedom and escape.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the new science building is not finished yet, but from the outside it looks great!", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Biology courses will cover all ____ human or animal body systems.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Copying from the internet has grown on a large ____ in recent years.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A large scale map shows a small ____ with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her grades will start to ____ unless she cuts back on the number of after-school activities she does.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the ____ cause of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When you get to the end of the page, do not stop. Please ____ reading on the next side.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to ____ the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What is your ____ of his recent odd behaviour?", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Earth's interior is divided into four layers, which is ____ of rocky planets.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the earth is closest to the sun, the ____ between the earth and sun is 147000000k.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to ____ to a speed of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In many cases, simply stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not ____ again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individual investors: ____ with caution.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to obtain a current bank ____ showing that you have enough funds to cover expenses.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Slavery is not an ____ which developed itself.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You must enter the US using the visa document issued by the ____ you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The employee asked his boss to ____ his salary.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must ____ with the death penalty regularly.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people think that terrorism is the greatest problem affecting ____ today.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the ____ damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many athletes who take ____ drugs risk serious, long-term damage to their health.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We can ____ that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such pressure.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This page unites the texts on various aspects of the history of law in the ____ world.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I asked for a ____ summary of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ all your PE clothes so that they can easily be returned to you if you lose them.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in ____ about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to determine ____ disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not ____ unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly ____ hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's ____ is that the bomb was set off by a recent immigrant.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These results indicate that ____ numbers of students attending the school are not attaining minimum levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have ____ to your medical record, thus is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the images and present them as a narrative or the story of destruction in New Orleans after Katrina.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is trying to ____ reading by having a small library of books in every classroom.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The communication ____ is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have access to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always fare well here, where patients may drive several hours to ____ medical care.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't think the government will ____ to persuade many people to recycle more of their garbage.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The management wanted to ____ the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to replace him.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so hostile to allowing ____ parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The soldier shot the dog for no ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The notion of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding ____ for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These drug companies were extremely negligent in that they failed to ____ consumers of the potential dangers associated with the use of their products.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Community ____ has helped me to realize the contradictions that we live in.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please remember to inspect any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other ____ to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student council can ____ suggestions, but it has no power to make changes happen.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The court also held that because of the contract between the classification ____ and the shipyard, the owners operated the ship under the French flag.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad ____ is put on a contract. If the contract is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a ____ excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Abortion is not a ____ right; it can be limited if the state wishes.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Using a new ____ to trap and measure single particles with lasers, an international group of researchers have demonstrated that Brownian motion of a single particle behaves differently than Einstein theorized one century ago.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "People might be surprised to know that a ____ situation had occurred in the US and that doctors and hospitals were allowed to override the family's wishes.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was not wise to use the river as the ____ for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Scientists ____ to unwrap the sweet mystery of the sugar coat on bacteria.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This ____ text contains the typical method of trisecting a segment.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher should ____ presentation styles and take into account diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What we are really discussing is whether the industrialized countries can ____ the pensions promised by their respective governments.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ was abandoned in 1842 because the speeches had become too long and because students refused to shorten them.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Importantly, he ____ that the Wabash River population appears to be stable.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police were unable to ____ the demonstrators from the town square.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The final topic presents the ____ of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical characteristic of ____ buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This course traces the ancient ____ of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The service ____ of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing ____.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This computer is the ____ of the school.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to settle the ____ by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students who have problems at home often seek the ____ of a trusted teacher at school.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise description of the aims and ____ of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will need to ____ a sample of recent writing so that your English level can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The idea was to remove the possibility of a ____ court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to label their products as high-, low- or ____ fat.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Women often earn less money that men doing the same job. This ____ must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In most countries the ____ for the place where you can get information is the letter 'i'.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't comply with police orders to ____ from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a tradition at the school for teachers to ____ a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a ____ decision, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest impact on my decision to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to ____ the plan on a regular basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most programs have experienced the need to develop mechanisms to ____ involvement of parents and/or guardians in the juvenile drug court process.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is fair to ____ the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment among older people.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is too soon to ____ the success of the \"war on terror\".", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Once Windows Movie Maker has opened, you will need to ____ the video clip that you would like to edit.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is an excellent report. The research is ____ and the writing clear.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to ____ the hierarchy and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her poor behaviour, but promised never to repeat it.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an ____ to enhance their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police were not ____ of controlling the street demonstrations. They had to call in the army.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These orders do much to ____ the significant need for better organization in terms of record-keeping.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all available sick leave for that ____ reporting period.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The doctrine of evolution was not considered to be a ____ hypothesis, worthy of investigation and in-depth study.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The two scholars are impressed with the ____ audience of readers their blog drew after their first three postings on Dec. 5, 2004.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this class, we will ____ the controversy about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The substantial advantages of these close personal relationships far ____ the disadvantages of remaining small.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its admissions policy to include more non-native speakers of English.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As we have seen in class on multiple occasions, these students become unmotivated and, as a result, inevitably ____ in school.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You must ____ a bibliography to all reports that are based on information found in books or on the internet.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is very little justice of the ____ and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to ____ problem-solving strategies that offer clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I am often surprised by the ____ of some high school students. One of them yesterday did not know the name of the president of the USA.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thorough cleaning must always ____ chemical disinfection of any equipment.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and ____ within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An athlete may begin training at age 6 but cannot ____ until age 8.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the immediate future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of education ____ strategies.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not dispose of the ____ at any price.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few precise facts.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in ____ to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They must not be allowed to ____ the emergence of a competitive market economy.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "only"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is only one ____ in your writing. You put: He play tennis instead of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Another well-known ____ of marijuana is its ability to increase appetite.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to ____ global problems, since they have also failed to ____ their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Women often earn less money that men doing the same job. This ____ must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company has the ____ to dismiss employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It takes a lot of ____ to cook a meal for 20 guests.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The USA is designing a spaceship that will land on Mars and ____ its polar regions.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I think that everyone going for the maximum marks, the highest grades and the greatest possible output is not the best ____ for a well-rounded individual.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to ____ whether antioxidants (Vitamins C and E) reduce the frequency of serious illness.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mrs Cho spoke on ____ of the Korean Parents Group and thanked the school for buying Korean books for the library.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not apply to Cheney's ____ force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ kind of language problem is to fill in the gap in a sentence with a missing word.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although nuclear ____ does not pollute the air, many people are against it because they fear an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear ____ station.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After much ____ the school has decided to admit students with physical disabilities.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to ____ if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ me by email if you need help understanding your assignment.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will collapse and whether the United States should ____ its collapse has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is ____ to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you don't receive search results within that time frame or if this an ____ request, please contact the reference desk.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This course traces the ____ concept of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To test for a ____ sentence, see if it can stand alone and still mean something.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Such web content does not necessarily ____ the opinions of the University administration.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was fined a large ____ of money for attempting to violate pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please ____ your disk, shut the disk drive and then click on 'Save'.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If we assume that the ____ of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My goal this ____ is to improve my mathematics and science grades.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She is trying to ____ a new way to open tin cans.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What is your interpretation of his recent ____ behaviour?", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "general"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Are you really doing everything you can to ____ for tests?", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our ____ was asked to make recommendations to reduce the friction between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the friction between teachers, parents and students, and ____ the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ will include several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will recur in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the ____.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government ____ produced a wide range of responses.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must ____ and strengthen existing laws and institute new procedures aimed at terrorists and criminals.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the magnitude of the ____ she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Someone forgot to ____ the book with the result that it contains serious errors of grammar or punctuation.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's not enough to ____ something; you have to work hard to achieve it.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The book provides good documentation of the ____ difficulties that confronted West Africans in Britain during the colonial period.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not an ideal solution by any means, as it limits researchers to a small percentage of the information they could ____ from these archives.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The cold, hard truth is that your parents' ____ was more open to experimentation, social change and an overall 'looser' way of life.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam ____ very heavily on voluntary workers.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The use of this seemingly simple system does not ____ an undeveloped technological ability on the part of 9th century Hindus.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ in Iraq continues to occupy the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Employees must have worked for the State for at least five years, and have a satisfactory ____ of sick leave usage and work performance.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One enjoyable way to improve in English is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Musical ability is a trait that some people are born with, but no-one succeeds as a musician without an ____ amount of practice.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I like teachers who can ____ clearly what we have to do.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Information Technology Committee has voted in favor of the ____ of requiring all incoming freshmen to have a computer.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you try to ____ something that is beyond the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are encouraged to commit to the therapy group for a sufficient amount of time before deciding that it is not the right ____ for you.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While addiction and drugs are serious problems in ____ that require a humane approach, there is no room for nonsense if we want to achieve success.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to specify in sufficient ____ the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous diagnosis or an inappropriate ____ recommendation.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This report draws on lessons learned from previous military deployments to consider strategies to ____ the health of troops in future deployments.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home underlie her recent ____ performance in school.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It seems probable that precise measurements of the ratio of ____ to negative responses will help to decide between the several processes.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most people ____ the airport's plans to finger-print all passengers as an expensive waste of time.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She had shown no ____ to engage in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One ____ group of bacteria, the \"blue-green algae,\" have left a fossil record that extends far back into the Precambrian Era.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Among other duties, Wren and his team of designers and builders were responsible for the upkeep or alteration of all ____ buildings.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you don't start working harder, we will ____ your right to leave the school at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most people do not like other parking their car outside their house, but they have no ____ to stop them.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to ____ flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "\"We hope to preserve the historic value of these buildings and ____ serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family member for the rest of their life ____ to this terrible form of cancer and they will deserve to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to ____ sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is ____ to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ that we find better and cheaper ways to create energy than by burning coal or oil.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the state was not able to ____ discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually ____ exceptional performance remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative ____ of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these ____s did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Take 3 grams of sodium chloride and an ____ amount of sugar.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After problems in the computer labs the school has decided to ____ entry to grade 12 students only.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bernstein argues that progressive reforms not only failed to increase the ____ of the people but were conservative and not innovative.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to ____ the vast mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There have been problems in the school ____ students of different nationalities.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The requirements threaten to decrease family and individual student control over the ____ process.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people accuse the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain ____ of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are a few meetings next week but the ____ conference doesn't start until on Monday 23.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are relocating to another U.S. school after your graduation, we will need to ____ your records to that school.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ your instinct as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A significant ____ to setting up a new business is the enormous amount of documentation that has to be completed.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has recently published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The ____ has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ danger to the soldiers is suicide bombers at the checkpoints.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, especially in the case of an ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has come under ____ to reduce the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An exciting and ____ teacher will receive more positive results than a teacher who is boring and low key.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Buying a lunch ticket in ____ will entitle you to a free drink.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have made no ____ to learn, thus you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How could his final test scores ____ so strongly from the predictions we made?", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will ____ the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is extremely important that you establish a strong ____ to return to your country after you complete your studies.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has made ____ progress towards its goal of reducing child poverty.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug abuse ____ many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An ____ will occur if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do not write on the board with ____ ink. It cannot be erased.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the ____ that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In 1993 a student wrote an article critical of Martin Luther King. The ____ was immediate and negative.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She would have a better chance of academic success if she didn't ____ in so many activities outside of school.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I often give the impression to my students that the demonstrations are spontaneous, but of ____ they are all prepared in advance.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The University of Maryland team is particularly focused on using their ____ to test drugs that may block cell-to-cell \"quorum-sensing\".", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over the course of the ____ there is a steady rise in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Hershey Corporation, however, already had a ____ to provide chocolate for the troops.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "However, his proposal contains a ____ that is important to recognize and understand.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the past 30 years, the ____ in Africa has continued to deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although we have already received a number of excellent proposals for papers, it has been decided to ____ the deadline for submissions.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not ____ a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people ____ the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many spiders can ____ seven different kinds of silk.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She ignored an ____ warning that she would be expelled if she did not start working harder.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is important to verify that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all ____ signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree that thought disorder and language disorder are ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Coca Cola is a name that is ____ to most people in the world.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Only the one that meets the ____ and sufficient conditions will win the election.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Several campus departments have been working to ____ the number of false alarms that result from controllable and mechanical factors.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a ____ basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some young people ____ their lives when they become addicted to drugs..", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There will be ____ of time for questions after each speaker finishes their presentation.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is known that organizations do not ____ readily or easily; many organizations that change do so in ways that are neither successful nor effective.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter prior to the announcement of sanctions, but did not ____ a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was also no apparent ____ of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She is going to fail the course unless there is a ____ improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "No consensus exists as to the ____ of the Hyde Amendment on the number of abortions or births.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In most countries the ____ for the place where you can get information is the letter 'i'.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can be ____ certain what you read at the government site is accurate and up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students will undertake comprehensive analysis of several works and will ____ a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Someone forgot to ____ the book with the result that it contains serious errors of grammar or punctuation.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The terrorist plane crashing into the New York tower is an ____ that most people will never forget.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He flew in with 500 rolls of film and 1400 pounds of provisions but forgot to ____ for the pilot to pick him up again.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Iron is a major ____ of hemoglobin that carries oxygen to all parts of the body.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you get a grade below C-, you will need to ____ the course for it to count at all on your major.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to ____ career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student will have an opportunity to be re-examined if the ____ attempt was not satisfactory.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Wikipedia is a wonderful ____ for high school students, but the information it contains must be checked for reliability.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many scientists ____ that the earth will be 3 degrees warmer by the end of the next century.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the departure times are not ____ for you, there is a list of recommended car and taxi services available as well.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no doubt about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is ____ dead.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Excellent public transportation was an important ____ in the decision to award the 2012 Olympics to London.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the applicant waits until the time of decision to complete this form, it can cause a serious ____ in obtaining the visa document.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you ____ your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to ____ a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has some loose plans to reduce ____ tax in the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Are you ____ sure that you gave me your homework?", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the ____ must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not ____ unless we as a department are willing to state explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Drug abusers also show prefrontal cortex ____ities; it is possible that ____ behaviour may be linked to drug use.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not correlate with the ____ to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I MUST see the headmaster at once! It's ____ !", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While I don't present this as ____ the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "too"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In many cases print journals are disappearing as librarians strive to ____ money and shelf space.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only authentic materials, not ones ____ made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be ____ for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the ____ decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The shortening of the lunch break caused ____ between the workers and the management.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Kennan had no ____ that the Soviets had regional, if not global, ambitions.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is ____ that you made no effort to learn the words for the test.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It seems that nothing will ____ her to get to class on time.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police have not been able to establish a ____ for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This research study will focus on the current practice of web writers and the ____ of the web pages they create.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad ____ is put on a contract. If the contract is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Congress seems to have taken a ____ approach to regulating a technology that is reinventing the very manner in which ideas are expressed.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to ____ an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you presume will come from the M31 ____ - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Sometimes, the author will ask that the decision to ____ a paper be reconsidered.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How can educators design ____ to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How do we approach the ____ and perpetual problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to ____ as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some scientists ____ that we cannot infer global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her problems began to manifest themselves after she was ____ for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to ____ a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to ____ by these two pieces, nor did I see any skill in the work.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy ____ to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At some time in the future we will need to make a total ____ from fossil fuel power, such as coal and oil, to renewable fuels such wind or sun energy.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ for writing such a report consists of the following steps: Choosing a subject; Finding sources of materials; Gathering the notes, etc.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A new ____ of skin replaces the damaged skin during healing.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has made ____ arrangements to control the number of demonstrators on the streets.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ability to ____ accurately and effectively is a vital component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have not got these words in the right order. In German the main verb must be the second ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is my firm ____ to remain with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do I have to be a ____ of the Society to submit a paper?", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory ____ of education have insufficient alternative educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Despite the political, economic and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not ____ into the interior of East.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most beginning ESL students need a lot of ____ from their teachers and parents before they can start to work more independently.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An ____ of this war is the rise of a large anti-war movement in the US.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are making very rapid ____ in learning English! You only started learning a year ago, and you can already speak quite fluently.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to improve student scores in standardized tests by doing 5 minutes practice at the start of every lesson.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be ____ for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although consultation between students in solving problems is encouraged, ____ answers will be considered plagiarized.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to ____ all your PE clothes so that they can easily be returned to you if you lose them.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her poor behaviour, but promised never to repeat it.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The lawyer was acting on ____ of the two children who had lost their parents in a car accident.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They did not provoke an ____. They responded to an ____ from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since the early 1990s, the number of smokers has continued to decrease but at the more gradual ____ of 5.2% annually.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The blue whale may be extinct by the end of the century unless we do all we can to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you accept a housing ____ in the Summer Allocation and subsequently cancel it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new version of Microsoft's Internet Explorer lets you ____ pictures by using the mouse ball and the Control key.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The boss was right to ____ that his workers would return to work once it was clear that they would otherwise lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With the passing of time the details of specific events ____ as they taken from the forefront of our mind and placed into the mainstream of our memory.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can exert ____ influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The State Department has seen a drastic ____ in passport applications being filed since a recent change in policy.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Design your syllabus so that it communicates to students what you expect them to learn and also how to ____ in achieving the learning goals for your course.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most comprehensive ____ of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Among other duties, Wren and his team of designers and builders were responsible for the upkeep or alteration of all ____ buildings.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was the result of his ____ that Brazil could afford scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would ____ an automatic decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to ____ the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a rational ____ but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Lord Wavell had to ____ as he could not bring about a settlement and he was succeeded by Lord Mountbatten.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We should never praise or blame any person on ____ of outward actions that are common to all; but only on ____ of their principles.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mechanisms by which comfrey can ____ the liver are unclear, but the main injury appears to be destruction of small veins, leading to cirrhosis.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They felt this was an unreliable ____ due to poor data and that the harvest could in fact increase.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This research study will focus on the current practice of web writers and the ____ of the web pages they create.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home ____ her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The system uses a novel inference engine that does not require users to explicitly ____ information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In the 20th century, if you wanted to kill lots of people, you needed a government ____ to do it.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Madrid attack was like the September 11 attack in that government agencies failed to share information about a ____ terrorist threat.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What might cause my computer to ____ oddly and even insult me, and how can I fix it?", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a ____ that is sometimes positive and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The chairman needs to ____ a better meeting next time. The last one was very disorganized.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The computer lab is ____ to the library.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I would like to know the ____ of what happened in the computer lab at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This report contains ____ problems, the most important of which is that it is not up to date.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most children take a share of ____ duties such as washing the dishes.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his intention to ____ at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people have complained about the ____ security procedures that have been introduced to UK airports.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An athlete may begin training at age 6 but cannot ____ until age 8.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Before making our decision we need to ____ the issue of financial support.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We used this information to construct a continuous ____ of the ratio of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The catheter then deploys a small balloon at the ____ of the blood clot.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are six categories to select from, each containing five answers in ascending ____ of difficulty.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Did anyone ____ to solve question 11?", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the mid-1930s, when she was back at Vogue as fashion editor, Nast declined to ____ her to editor of the magazine, once again because of the morality issue.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to address the issue of global warming. They ____ it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the ____ Protestant denominations in Europe did not oppose the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a new computer for each of its teachers.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most language teachers use ____ aids in the classroom, such as pictures or objects.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of ____ to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is liable to ____ the course.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Every piece of ____ ground in the town centre has already been built on.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To ____ these opportunities, information systems will need to sense and act as well as compute.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round cycle of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Nancy Tsai knew from experience that the housing ____ for graduate students living off campus was bleak.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Only seniors have the ____ of using this room. You will have to wait until you are in grade 12.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Germany had to ____ a harsh peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to ____ over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of ____ choices that a criminal would make in the decision to commit a crime.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In order to claim a project, you must ____ a team of 3 to 6 people within a class and get verbal approval from your professor.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It took the Brazilian football player a little while to ____ to the speed and hardness of the English football league.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all available sick leave for that ____ reporting period.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The role of public schools in the ____ of these disturbed children is controversial.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Bone marrow may ____ cells lost in vision diseases.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will ____ to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is thinking of extending ____ education by two years.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used ____ to acquire food.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school does not have ____ money to build a new cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the quantity of ____ now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One can fill a small book just describing the commonsense knowledge needed to solve an ____ problem like how to get to the airport.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is especially true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and ____ complex.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only employ workers with ____, but how do young people gain that ____ if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "17% reported that their ____ was not at all adequate.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Court determined, however, that evidence concerning Ms. Lewinsky was not ____ to the core issues in this case.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was a loud ____ in the cafeteria today. I had to intervene before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is still too soon to ____ how important this invention will be.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This piece of work is much ____ to your last one. I'm glad to see you are getting better.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A common science experiment for young people is to ____ the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teaching ____ is under siege from an increasing number of social, economic and political factors, leading to large, unmanageable classrooms.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I thoroughly ____ this book to anybody interest in the vegetation of North America and to those studying similar vegetation in other parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She will ____ her chances of graduating unless she starts to attend school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "So if they go extinct on one tropical mountain there is only a ____ chance that they will recolonize from a similar nearby mountain.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Coca Cola is a name that is ____ to most people in the world.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Design your syllabus so that it communicates to students what you expect them to learn and also how to ____ in achieving the learning goals for your course.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I believe that the most important event in my ____ is the war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It must be ____ what the primary theme of each section is, and how that theme connects with the paper's overall theme.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Let's make it clear from the beginning that there is no one thing that you can do to ____ everyone, or even to ____ the same person every time.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Student Activities Committee presented a project designed to ____ awareness of the ongoing crisis in the Sudan.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no ____ about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is virtually dead.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will ____ due to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a stable domestic ____ would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She has a lot of ____ in tennis; in fact she's the best player in her grade!", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full ____ as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ the space it has made available for computers and video screens.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This document explains why it is important to conduct a ____ assessment during a sustainability project.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to ____ much discussion among teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Gandhi, who brought independence to India, was an ____ man.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you order a book from Amazon, you usually ____ it within a few days.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To develop a ____ approach to business, managers must utilize the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do you think that the school will ____ the suggestion to increase the number of holidays?", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random ____ of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Top American scientists assigned to the weapons hunt in Iraq found no ____ Saddam Hussein was making chemical weapons.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important that the government does not ____ significantly from what it promised during the elections.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of teaching is to help students become independent learners.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They are planning to ____ a new bridge behind the school.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad attitude is put on a ____. If the ____ is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no ____ upon her behaviour at home. She is allowed to do whatever she wants.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ how much her excellent grade is due to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Madrid attack was like the September 11 attack in that government agencies failed to share information about a ____ terrorist threat.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Military power is not an appropriate tool to ____ the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest ____ resolutions.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He had to ____ the fact that teaching was not the right job for him.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is vital that we find better and cheaper ways to ____ energy than by burning coal or oil.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not acknowledge the ____ developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Major life events often ____ changes in financial planning strategies.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is important for teachers to create a positive learning ____ in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The university follows a strict ____ of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The relationship between Christianity and the Enlightenment remains a ____ issue in the history of Western civilization.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Another significant ____ was provided by the results of the post-hoc test of Recognition Motivation.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students who have problems at home often ____ the counsel of a trusted teacher at school.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows bias ____ the Germans.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "UK airports have increased the ____ of security staff since the terrorist attacks in London.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to ____ and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government neither intends to comment on the ____ nor even to admit that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government survey produced a wide ____ of responses.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would ____ and reject that heritage.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school had to pay a small ____ to the parents of the boy who hurt his arm on the ski trip.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total ____ of mail does not decrease and the postal service does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although we did train the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our training was not thorough enough to ____ them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the ____ plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ produced a wide range of responses.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Another reason to ____ student e-mail and internet usage is to ensure their safety.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It would be easy to overlook important biological information that did not ____ itself in visible symptoms or test results.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For financial reasons the government had to cut the ____ to help prisoners on their release from jail.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted control than where it lost ____ of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a ____ transition.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Smoking will probably ____ in popularity in most western countries now that smoking bans are in force.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Allies decided that Korea could not ____ itself after so many years of foreign rule.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Rubin did not suffer ____ but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you want to have a more interesting style of presentation, vary the ____ and tone of your voice.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company does a minor amount of business in the USA; the majority of its ____ is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't appreciate a ____ from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has stated that it will not ____ its decision to ban smoking in pubs.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to improve the performance of these devices, but ____ there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Workers will ____ to where wages are higher.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The only goal of some people is to ____ as much money as possible.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the precaution to take if you decide to use email as an ____ means of communication.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the ____ government agencies did not connect the dots.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Potts announced that he planned to ____ a broadly based committee of representatives to study the Indian issue.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your homework planner! You will have to buy a new one.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was a ____ move, but frankly we didn't have a choice.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is possible to ____ the world by boat in about three days.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student who had forgotten his homework was ____ that the teacher was absent that day.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government was fully ____ of the magnitude of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a ____ challenge for society in general.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is trying to ____ a new way to open tin cans.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The suggestion is ____ not reasonable, and the department need not adopt it.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ heavier punishment for dropping litter in the streets.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor condition and are in ____ need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must ____ it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main ____ to such Research & Development programs is the fact that the market size and the prices of the new products are unknown.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government reduced its ____ to the Arts Council after it was found that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The one ____ in the classroom that belongs to me is the old typewriter.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She began to notice that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that people eat 5 fruits or vegetables every day.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Prior to the change, students had the option of taking a track that didn't ____ language proficiency.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I prefer to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different ____ to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It seems probable that precise measurements of the ____ of positive to negative responses will help to decide between the several processes.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The workers participated in an ____ to see if they worked harder with music in the background.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students gain professional ____ before graduation so that they enter the job market with a distinct advantage.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How can employees ____ whether they have a disability under the new regulations?", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The workers were not ____ of the management's plans to relocate the factory.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ is predominantly concerned with the social relations of power that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Should the government ____ more in solar energy or nuclear energy? It's a difficult choice.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When police investigate a crime, they look for ____ such as fingerprints, specks of blood, etc.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Which do you ____ the more: health or wealth?", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a convenient way to ____ energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Simply exporting surplus graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a ____ for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Slave remains appeared during an excavation at the ____ of these ruins.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the next 50 years the world's weather could ____ significantly if the polar ice continues to melt.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston ____ had a bold idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The former assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more ____ idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative ____ of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these ____s did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The reporter is interested in the proportion of ____ school teachers who have at least 20 years of experience.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in ____ and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From my perspective as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a logical ____ of having free will.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Melting glaciers will ____ Alpine ski resorts within 45 years, says report.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Children are able to ____ between reality and fantasy between the ages of 3 and 5, according to new research.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a ____ corner of Antarctica can disrupt an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the ____ occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and ____ the extent of the problem.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to align commercial and financial practices in its ____ countries.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in ____ but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This article will only ____ the issues rather than present a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and ____ him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In fact, most nations do not ____ immigrants for permanent settlement.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She will be a great ____ to the school when she retires next month. She has been a wonderful teacher here for many years.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will not prevail unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in ____ service.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to ____ drought a month or more in advance for most locations.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As a ____ of the efforts over this last year, SAGE was able to donate books to more than 30 deserving schools in Illinois.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his intention to ____ the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}]]